https://www.perdoceoed.com/privacy

UPDATED PERDOCEO EDUCATION PRIVACY POLICY – YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
Effective Date: January 2014. Last Updated: December 31, 2019
THIS POLICY APPLIES TO THE SITES AND APPS WHERE IT APPEARS.
This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information collected on our sites and apps where it is located. This also includes how we treat information collected when you use our Wi-Fi services. We refer to these as our "Platforms." This policy does not apply to information we collect in other ways, such as information we collect from you in connection with your course work. This policy also does not apply to our privacy obligations under FERPA and similar state laws. To learn more, please visit here for the AIU FERPA Notice or here for the CTU FERPA Notice
WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM AND ABOUT YOU
We collect contact information. For example, we may collect your name and mailing address. This may include your zip code. We might also collect phone numbers and email addresses.
We collect application and tuition information. For example we collect this information in your application for admission and financial aid. This includes Social Security number and date of birth. It also includes citizenship or military status. We may also collect information about other schools you have attended and income history. We might also collect your credit card or bank account number and billing address. For more information about how we treat education records and financial information, please view the FERPA Notices linked above.
We collect information you post or submit. We collect information you post in a public space on our Platforms. This may include posts you make on course discussion boards or our social media pages. We may also collect your social media profile information. We might also collect the information you submit to us, such as through our live chat feature.
We collect job application information. If you apply for a job through our Platform, we collect the information you include in your application. For example, this may include the name and address of your employer and your employment history.
We collect demographic information. We may collect your age and gender. We may also collect information about your race or ethnicity.
We collect device and location information. We collect the type and make of device you use to access our Platforms. We may also collect information about the browser you are using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We may collect information across the devices you use to access our Platform. If you use our app, we might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it. This might include your device identification number, IP address or mobile operating system. We may also collect location information.
WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU IN SEVERAL WAYS
We collect information directly from you. For example, we might collect information when you request information about our products and services or sign up for an event. We might also collect information when you sign up to receive communications from us.
We collect information from you passively. We use common tracking technologies to collect information passively. This includes when you use our Platforms or our WiFi services.
We collect information from third parties. We may receive information about you from other sources. This might include our business partners. It may also include our education partners, such as organizations that administer college-level exams, manage records related to education, or provide scholarships, grants and other financial aid. It might also include other academic institutions. It also includes friends who use our referral features. We may also get information about you from social media platforms.
WE COMBINE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN FROM DIFFERENT SOURCES
We may combine information that we collect offline with information we collect online. We may also combine information you submit or that we track across multiple devices. We may also combine information we collect from you with information we get about you from others.
WE USE INFORMATION IN A VARIETY OF WAYS.
We use your information to communicate with you. This includes responding to your questions or inquiries or notifying you if you won a promotion. We will also use your information to send you information about your account or about our relationship. We may send push notifications in our apps.
We use information to provide you with our products and services. This includes determining your eligibility for our services. It also includes fulfilling your requests.
We use your information to understand your interests and improve our products and services. We may use your information to make our Platform, products and services better. This may include improving student retention and user experience. We may also use your information to customize your experience with us. For example, we may use your information to determine your interest in our products and services or to better understand what products and services interest you.
We use your information for marketing purposes. We may provide you with information about current or new products and services or other ads. We might use your information to serve you with ads. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may also have our business partners serve you with ads about our products and services. We may use your geolocation information to send these communications.
We use information for security purposes. This could include protecting our family of companies and our students. It may also include protecting our Platform.
We use information as otherwise permitted or required by law or as we may notify you.. This includes using your information for our legitimate business needs.
WE SHARE INFORMATION WITH SERVICE PROVIDERS AND THIRD PARTIES
We share your information within the Perdoceo Education Corporation family of companies. This includes our network of schools and the Perdoceo Education Foundation Scholarship Fund
We share your information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.. For example, this may include payment processors or companies that provide identity verification services. It may also include companies that fulfill transcript requests or send communications on our behalf.
We share information with our business partners. For example, this may include third parties that provide educational products and services related to our business. It may also include social media sites or a third party that co-sponsors a promotion.
We share information with those who help pay for your education. We may share your information with family members or employers who help pay your tuition. We may also share information with banks or other lenders that provide education loans to you. For more information about how we treat education records and financial information, please visit the FERPA notices linked above.
We share information with third parties for marketing purposes. This may include third parties that serve ads on our behalf. This may also include third parties in whose products or services we believe you may be interested. These third parties may also share your information with others. These third parties may use your information for their own marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of others. This may include the delivery of interest-based advertising.
Your information may be publicly accessible on our Platforms. Information you submit in chat rooms or other features can be seen by others who use that features. This may include information about you like the courses in which you are enrolled. It may also include your contact information.
We will share your information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if all or part of our business is sold, we may share your personal information with the new owner. This may include as part of an asset sale, corporate reorganization or other change of control.
We share information with regulating agencies and government entities. We may share your information with the organizations that analyze our education practices and provide our qualifications to operate as an educational institution. We may also share information with government agencies if we believe we are required to in order to comply with the law or as part of our business operations. For more information about how we treat education records and financial information, please visit the FERPA notices linked above.
We will share information to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. This includes responding to a court order or subpoena. It could also include sharing information if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating a potential fraud. This could include fraud we think has occurred during a sweepstakes or promotion. We may also share information if you are the winner of a sweepstakes or other contest with anyone who requests a winner’s list.
We will share information for other reasons we may describe to you.
YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you receive from us. Note that even if you opt out of our promotional emails, you will still receive transactional messages from us.
You can control certain cookies and tracking tools. To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our Do Not Track Policy, please click here
You can control tools your mobile devices. For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone.
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Pursuant to the California "Shine the Light" law of 2003 , if you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an email at privacymatters@perdoceoed.com or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your email or letter that you are a California resident making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry.
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) of 2018
creates new consumer rights relating to the access to, deletion of, and sharing of personal information for California residents. Please see Appendix A – California Specific Privacy Notice for all required information, including your rights under the CCPA and how to submit a request.
YOUR NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you reside in Nevada, you have the right to ask us at any time to review the personal information that we have collected through our website(s) or the services we provide and to request changes. Subject to the terms of applicable Nevada law , you may also submit a request directing us not to sell certain covered personal information we have collected or will collect about you. To make a request, please send us an email at privacymatters@perdoceoed.com or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your email or letter that you are a Nevada resident making a "Nevada Internet Privacy" inquiry.
OUR PLATFORMS AND CHILDREN.
Our Platforms are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has provided us with information, please contact us at privacymatters@perdoceoed.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this website Policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request." Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line here.
WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES
The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our Platform will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. We use reasonable means to safeguard personal information under our control. User IDs and passwords are needed to access certain areas of our Platform. It is your responsibility to protect your username and password.
STORAGE OF INFORMATION
Information we maintain may be stored in the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your personal information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not provide the same level of protections as those in your own country. We may retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
WE MAY LINK TO THIRD PARTY SITES.
Our Platform may contain links to other third party sites that are not governed by this Policy. If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to a site we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices used by third party sites. We suggest that you read the privacy policies of those sites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our privacy practices contact us at privacymatters@perdoceoed.com or by telephone at 847-781-3600. You may also write to us at the following address:
Privacy Matters
Perdoceo Education Corporation
231 N. Martingale Road
Schaumburg, IL 60173
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
From time to time, we may update or revise this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our Platforms. Please check our Platforms periodically for updates.
©
Perdoceo Education Corporation. All rights reserved.
